janestreet.com 2019-12-20

# Jane Street Ad and Cookie Policy :: Jane Street

## Jane Street Privacy Policy

Effective Date: March 21, 2017; Last Updated: May 18, 2018

#### This Privacy Policy applies to the sites where it appears.

This Policy describes how Jane Street treats the personal information we collect from visitors to the websites where this policy appears. This policy does not apply to your offline relationship with us. If you have offline dealings with us in Europe, for example as a client of Jane Street Financial Limited, please click here to view the applicable privacy policy.

By interacting with us, you consent to our privacy practices.

#### What information we collect.

**We collect contact information.** We collect information when you apply for a job or internship, and when you sign up to receive emails, to attend events or to enter contests. Information we collect includes your name and email address, and may also include your phone number and address as well as your title and company name, or school affiliation.

**We collect job history and related information.** We collect job history from job and internship applicants. This includes information you submit as part of your resume.

**We permit you to post content on our site.** Where you post comments to our sites, for example, on our Tech Blog, your posts will be publicly viewable.

**We collect usage information.** We collect information about the browser and computer you use to access our website. This might include your IP address. We might also collect information identifying the sites you visit before and after visiting our websites. To learn more about our passive information activities please read our Ad and Cookie Policy.

#### How we collect information.

**We collect information you provide.** We collect information when you submit it online such as when you sign up to attend events, to receive emails, or to enter contests.

**We collect information from you passively.** We use tracking tools like browser cookies and web beacons to collect information about your use of the website over time. We may have third parties collect personal information this way. Learn more about these tools and how you can control them in our Ad and Cookie Policy.

**We get information about you from third parties.** Our third-party partners and associates may give us information about you. These might include social media websites.

**We combine information.** We combine information that we have collected from various sources, such as offline, online, and information we get from third parties.

#### How we use information.

**We use information to respond to your requests or questions.** We use your information to process your requests. This might include a job application or notifying you about events.

**We use information to run and improve our websites and our business.** We might use your information to measure and analyze our websites. This helps us make our websites better.

**We use information for security purposes.** We use information to protect our company, our clients, or our websites.

**We use information to send you communications.** We might provide you with information about Jane Street or services or events in which we think you would be interested. We may contact you about your relationship with us. We may also contact you about this Policy or our website Terms.

**We may use information as otherwise permitted by law or as we may notify you.**

**If you are in Europe:** Our basis for processing your information is typically to perform a contract, based on consent or for our legitimate interests.

**We will share information within the Jane Street family of companies.**

**We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf.** We share information with vendors who help us manage our website or send or store emails on our behalf. We also provide information to vendors who provide human resource support. We may also share information with third parties that assist us in driving job applicants to our website. Some vendors may be located outside of the United States and outside of the European Economic Area.

**We may share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves.** We will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena or if a government agency or investigatory body requests. This includes sharing information with the US government. We also share information when we are investigating potential fraud. We will also include your information in a publicly-available winner’s list if you are the winner of a promotion.

**We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business as permitted by law.** We may give our job applicant records as part of a sale of a business unit. Where legally required, we will give you prior notice and, if you have the legal right to do so, allow you to object.

**We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you or as permitted by law.**

#### You have certain choices about how we use your information.

**You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails.** To stop receiving promotional emails from the Tech Blog or the Morning Note, follow the instructions in those email messages. Even if you opt out of receiving marketing messages, we may continue to send you other types of messages. For example, we may still contact you in response to job applications or events. To request deletion of your information, please email us at [privacy-policy@janestreet.com](mailto:privacy-policy@janestreet.com).

**You can control cookies and tracking tools.** To learn how to manage cookies and other tracking tools, and to read our **Do Not Track** policy, please click here.

**You have other controls you can exercise.** You can choose whether or not to share personal information. If you choose not to share, some parts of our websites and some services may be more difficult or impossible to use. To update or correct your information, you can email us at [privacy-policy@janestreet.com](mailto:privacy-policy@janestreet.com).

#### These sites are not intended for, or appealing to, children.

Our sites are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally-identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, please email us at [privacy-policy@janestreet.com](mailto:privacy-policy@janestreet.com). Please mark your inquiries “COPPA Information Request.”

#### We use standard security measures.

**The Internet is not 100% secure.** We cannot promise that your use of our sites will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet.

We keep personal information as long as it is needed or relevant for our business. We also keep information as required by law.

#### We collect and store information both in and outside of the United States.

Information that we collect from you may be transferred to and stored within the United States, the United Kingdom, the Netherlands and Hong Kong. If you live outside of these jurisdictions you understand and agree that we may transfer your information to the United States or Hong Kong. This site is subject to US laws, which may not afford the same level of protection of those in your country.

#### We may link to third-party sites or services we don’t control.

If you click on some links on our sites, you will be taken to websites we do not control. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of those websites. We are not responsible for these third-party sites or services.

#### Feel free to contact us if you have more questions.

If you have any questions about this Policy or want to access, delete, or correct your information, please email us at [privacy-policy@janestreet.com](mailto:privacy-policy@janestreet.com).

You can also write to us at:

  * Jane Street
  * c/o Legal and Compliance
  * 250 Vesey Street, 6th Floor
  * New York, NY 10281

#### What we will do if there is an update to this policy.

From time to time we may change our privacy practices. We will notify you of any material changes to this policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our website. Please check our site periodically for updates.
